This new plane flies faster than sound,
but quietly. And it's a big deal for
bringing back supersonic planes that you
can fly in. Because you used to be able
to go from New York to London in less
than 3 and 1/2 hours on a commercial
plane, but all that changed when the
Concorde stopped flying. Largely because
countries banned the boom it makes when
it passes by. But this plane's long nose
and wide delta wings and T-tail let it
slip through the air minimizing that
boom, and its smooth underside sends
most of the boom up, which together turn
that loud boom on the ground into more
like a thud, no louder than distant
thunder. This recent flight tested the
plane's controls and how it handles
aerodynamic [music] stress, getting one
step closer to you on a supersonic
plane. I got to see this plane up close,
so if you want to see it, subscribe.